Guide to the Arleen Schloss Papers MSS.437
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Performances and Exhibitions, 1960-2013; 82.4 Linear Feet in 44 cassette boxes, 33 record cartons, 12 manuscript boxes, 5 LP boxes, 5 flat files, and 4 flat boxes; 665 audiocassettes; 202 Hi8; 170 VHS; 137 MiniDV; 78 U-matic; 58 Quarter_Inch_Audio_Reel; 29 Half_Inch_Video_Reel; 4 Betamax
  - Subseries I.C: Events by Date, 1967-2013
    - A and Claire Fergusson, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0351)
    - A and ORF / Original Austria Edit, undated (Box 120, Vhs 437_1210)
    - ABC Layers, undated (Box 84, Audiocassette 437_0811)
    - "ABC No Rio", undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Alan's place, undated (Box 107, Minidv 437_2402)
    - Allen Toussaint Retrospective, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0348)
    - Alphabet with Reverb, undated; cuid44178 (Box 154, Quarter inch audio reel 437_2427)
    - Alphabet, undated (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0566)
    - Alphabets, Runaway ball, Paint, Marbles, undated (Box 116, U-matic 437_1079)
    - AM Songs, undated
      - Part one (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0499)
      - Part one (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0580)
      - Part two (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0492)
      - Part two (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0583)
      - Part two (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0585)
      - Part three (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0478)
      - Part three (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0586)
      - Ends of parts one, two, and three (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0497)
    - Amable, Nik A, John Cage, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1530)
    - Angel sings, Terry, undated (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0878)
    - Anne Barbe Rough Mix, undated (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0605)
      Note on label reads: "This is rough mix 2 give u an idea of some things"
    - Anthony de Mare / Merkin, undated (Box 124, Vhs 437_1405)
    - A's Saloon, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - "A's X Billy Bell" Installation, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Arleen's piece, undated (Box 88, Audiocassette 437_0953)
    - Arleen Schloss Performance, undated (Box 144, U-matic 437_2168)
    - "The Arts Friends Show," Artibus Sacrum, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - "Artworks from Arleen Schloss" exhibit diagram, undated (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - "As She Sees It," "A-Z Around the World", undated (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0574)
    - Artists Talk on Art, undated
      - Part one (Box 97, Minidv 437_1543)
      - Part two (Box 96, Minidv 437_1512)
    - "Assembling at Midnight: Mini Avant Garde Festival", undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - "Audioarchive: Women of the 80's" Installation, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - A-Z -- Proposal, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Barbara, undated (Box 136, Vhs 437_1761)
    - Barbara Hammann F-A concert, Connie castle, undated (Box 140, Vhs 437_1865)
    - Barbara Holland, undated (Box 70, Audiocassette 437_0223)
    - Bare Bones Orchestra -- "Money On My Mind", undated (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0340)
    - The Baroque Art of Telemann, undated (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0393)
    - Beatles, undated (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0148)
    - Benefit party, the Kitchen, undated (Box 90, Hi8 437_1262)
    - Big Guitar, Richard M., undated (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0835)
      Full label reads: "Side A: Big guitar, 4 big guitar, Richard M(label smudged) Trombone / Side B: Sweet dreams, What a feeling, rain storm, sirens"
    - Blanchard, Sterling, Gibson #5, undated (Box 103, Hi8 437_2193)
    - Blässe live in Düsseldorf, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0360)
    - Blonde Fox, undated (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0161)
    - Blondie -- "Eat to the Beat", undated (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0321)
    - Blondie, undated (Box 137, Vhs 437_1784)
    - Bob Dylan -- "Empire Burlesque", undated (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0149)
    - Bowie, undated (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0730)
    - Bowie Shoot, undated (Box 135, Vhs 437_1709)
    - Bowie, Tin Machine, Reed, New York, undated (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0938)
    - "Brains" by Revlon, Jack Water, undated (Box 135, Vhs 437_1704)
    - "Brave New World", undated (Box 116, U-matic 437_1080)
    - Brazilian music, undated
      - Audio (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0065)
      - Audio (Box 88, Audiocassette 437_0951)
    - Bremen, undated (Box 114, Vhs 437_1032)
    - Brian Adam Exhibition, C.o.L.A., undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Bruce Wands, undated (Box 107, Minidv 437_2351)
    - Brucknerhaus #2 -- Opening party, undated (Box 104, Hi8 437_2225)
    - Butch Morris, undated (Box 78, Audiocassette 437_0582)
    - Canned Heat -- Evil Woman, undated (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0691)
    - Castle Rehearsal, Performance at Linz, undated (Box 132, U-matic 437_1673)
    - "Cash / Newhouse" Exhibition, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Ce Rosa, Filmori East, Johnny About A, undated (Box 101, Hi8 437_2089)
    - Chelsea taped by Peter R. Meyer, undated (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0127)
    - Chinese Opera, undated
      - In loft (Box 135, Vhs 437_1730)
      - Night (Box 131, Vhs 437_1695)
    - Clayton, undated (Box 107, Minidv 437_2380)
    - The Coachmen Demo, undated (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0314)
    - Concerts, undated (Box 125, U-matic 437_1232)
    - Connie and Bob, Suzi's poem, undated (Box 92, Hi8 437_1312)
    - Country music, Waylon magazine, undated (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0312)
    - Charlie Rose MS, undated (Box 95, Minidv 437_1449)
    - "Chance Talks", undated (Box 136, Vhs 437_1751)
    - "Childbirth" Performance, White Columns, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Christa Jack copy, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1474)
    - Color Mirror, shot of Nik, undated (Box 100, Hi8 437_2057)
    - Compilation Tape -- Alphabet Inner Tube, Shot Dot Shot, "Rubber Bands," "AAA", undated (Box 95, Minidv 437_1463)
    - Compilation Tape -- Ella in Berlin, Mack the Knife, Alberta Hunter, Amtrack Blues, Scraggle Arilp, Billie Holiday "Lady in Satin", undated (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0350)
    - Compilation Tape -- John Good Gallery, White Columns, Jack Tilton Gallery, Exit Art, undated (Box 94, Hi8 437_1377)
      Originally bound by rubber band with 437_1376, 437_1379; Label reads: "Dan Flavin - John Good Gallery / White Columns - group show / P.P.O.W. / Jack Tilton Gallery / Exit Art"
    - Compilation Tape -- Stadtgalerie #2, Henry, "Bottles, "Letters," "Eat - Eye" prints, show films to class, "Rubberbands," Susi, undated (Box 136, Vhs 437_1747)
    - Compilation Tape -- Studio pass, China talk at Artists Space, Marble faces, Connie's show, Marbles, Broadway, A at Met, undated (Box 101, Hi8 437_2077)
    - Computer with Lettie and Kevin, undated (Box 106, Minidv 437_2319)
    - Connecticut, Marvin Minsky Part 1, undated (Box 143, Vhs 437_1927)
    - Connie Camera, Castle Rehearsals and Performances in Town, undated (Box 120, Vhs 437_1188)
    - Cowgirl Hall of Fame, undated (Box 103, Hi8 437_2200)
    - Craig Burk -- "Shrug", undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0352)
    - The Cubiculo Performance with Elina Mooney, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Cyn and Nina, undated (Box 107, Minidv 437_2387)
    - "Dancing Over Quicksand" Exhibition, Wooster Gallery, undated (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Dreams in Dialogue Staccato Opera -- Proposal, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Dalai Lama, undated (Box 114, Vhs 437_1045)
    - Dance Tape, undated (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0128)
    - Dance Tape with Lynn, undated (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0535)
    - David Boyle, undated (Box 135, Vhs 437_1732)
    - de Kooning and the Met, undated (Box 135, Vhs 437_1734)
    - Dig Cliches, Tim, undated (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0118)
    - Do Monkey Presents, undated (Box 151, U-matic 437_0022)
    - Duck Rock and Malcolm McLaren Performance, 8BC, undated (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0698)
    - "Earworks: An Exhibition of Musical Scores and Sound Art," Grommet Gallery, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - E. F. Higgins -- Master Edit, undated (Box 137, Vhs 437_1790)
    - E.F. Higgins, Richard Edson, undated (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0274)
    - Electron Macroscope, undated (Box 151, Half inch video reel 437_0024)
    - Engelbert, Julio's tape, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0344)
    - Eno -- "Taking Tiger by Strategy", undated (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0154)
    - Eric Bogosian, undated (Box 107, Minidv 437_2395)
    - Exit Art, undated (Box 106, Minidv 437_2320)
    - Eye, Berlin, undated (Box 89, Hi8 437_1241)
    - Eyes through Marbles, undated (Box 130, Vhs 437_1641)
    - From "Flame", undated (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0096)
    - From Bantara Eve, Rosenthal, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0366)
    - Georgi Ana Liccione Steward -- Bean Bag Activities, Songs and Music, undated (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0937)
    - Georges Teyssot, undated (Box 135, Vhs 437_1719)
    - German Spearla and C., Cummings Symposium #4, undated (Box 104, Hi8 437_2227)
    - Gibson, Doro, Pauline #6, undated (Box 98, Hi8 437_2000)
    - Glen's Notes, undated (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0137)
      Full label reads: "Side A: Glen's notes - 4 movements to 3 movements, oscillator / Side B: London Radio world news, weather, Summit, Regent hatcher, Beatles - Here Comes the Sun, Blip, Funny English Stuff - Glen's notes"
    - The Golem, undated (Box 92, Hi8 437_1314)
    - Gospel and Special, undated (Box 82, Audiocassette 437_0731)
    - Gracie, undated (Box 120, Vhs 437_1217)
    - Gregorio, undated (Box 90, Minidv 437_2291)
    - Guided Yoga -- Ernest Shaw, undated (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0041)
    - Hard painting, camera 2, undated (Box 91, Hi8 437_1280)
    - Hedda Sterne Exhibit, undated
      - #1, Raw material (Box 135, Vhs 437_1716)
      - #2, End of opening, Hedda's paintings (Box 93, Hi8 437_1341)
      - Hedda Sterne at Gallery (Box 140, Vhs 437_1867)
      - Opening and Barn Mix Performance, East Hampton (Box 135, Vhs 437_1714)
    - Hennie, undated (Box 88, Minidv 437_0970)
    - Hockney and Fishel, undated (Box 90, Hi8 437_1272)
    - Hockney at Enid's, undated (Box 91, Hi8 437_1282)
    - Holly #2, undated (Box 107, Minidv 437_2391)
    - Holly's piece, undated (Box 128, Vhs 437_1601)
    - Howie solo, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0353)
    - HSU Bling, Bork Opening and Exhibit, undated (Box 101, Hi8 437_2065)
    - Ilona Malka Rich, undated (Box 89, Minidv 437_0996)
    - "IS IT" Exhibition, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - "It's A" Performance -- Original Score, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Jajouka, Brian Jones, Nusrat Ali Khan, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0342)
    - Jajouka -- Music of Morocco, undated (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0162)
    - James and Luna, undated (Box 98, Hi8 437_1987)
    - James Joyce, E.E. Cummings, Dylan Thomas reading their work, undated (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0140)
    - Jane Johnston, Dental Direct, Eastsiders, undated (Box 124, Vhs 437_1577)
    - Jaron Linier, undated (Box 95, Minidv 437_1426)
    - Jaron Lanier #3, Tapal, undated (Box 104, Hi8 437_2224)
    - Jaz Blu Psymask, undated (Box 97, Minidv 437_1546)
    - Jennifer Warner, Leonard Cohen, undated (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0152)
    - Joachim, Marika's raw material, undated (Box 136, Vhs 437_1746)
    - Jodell, undated (Box 93, Hi8 437_1359)
      Label also reads: "Human Issues, Inc."
    - Joe Lewis, Peter Cummings, undated (Box 70, Audiocassette 437_0234)
    - John Smead, undated (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0145)
    - John Smead -- "Bones In a Hole," "Score Connect", undated
      - Audio, undated (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0332)
      - Video, undated (Box 144, Vhs 437_2141)
    - John W. Master, undated (Box 90, Hi8 437_1277)
    - Joseph Beuys, The Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, undated (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0150)
    - Ken Drawing, Raining Men, Derick, Eric, Kisha, Kendel, undated (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0757)
    - Krupps Stahlwerksinfonie, undated
      - Audio (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0130)
      - Komödii Trakik, Collection No. 2 (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0367)
    - Kwang Yu Fong, children, undated (Box 89, Minidv 437_0993)
    - Kwok's friend, Mr. Ma, undated (Box 94, Hi8 437_1390)
    - L, P, Y, C, H, G, J, W, X, Q, B, R, M, O, U, T, A, undated (Box 103, Hi8 437_2203)
    - Lang composite, Maureen, Brittles, undated (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0685)
    - Larry King Weekend, undated (Box 90, Minidv 437_2286)
    - Laser, Dome, undated (Box 152, Half inch video reel 437_0027)
    - Laura Logic, Deutsch Amerikanische Freundschaft, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0337)
    - Le Bells, undated; cuid44179 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0001)
    - Le Bomba, undated (Box 151, Half inch video reel 437_0025)
    - Life Lines Slopes, undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0088)
    - Light forms, undated (Box 107, Minidv 437_2366)
    - "Limbo Refugee Camp" Saturday Night Series at A's, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Linus Coraggio, undated
      - Part one (Box 107, Minidv 437_2393)
      - Part two (Box 107, Minidv 437_2394)
    - Lisa Mayo -- "Spiderwoman," Theater Inc., undated (Box 138, U-matic 437_1829)
    - "Live Performance from AZ," Europe, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1472)
    - Live TV Performance #10, undated (Box 104, Hi8 437_2228)
      Label also reads: "September 14/15, interviews, Gerbel, Klany (?) - Karl, skim"
    - London Performance, undated (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0476)
    - Los Tropics, Nemo Hill, undated (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0276)
    - Lou Reed, Marcy Playground, undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0091)
    - Lou Reed Berlin, Wilson Pickett, undated (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0114)
    - Lower East Side Summer, Shuttle Theater, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Lynne Kanter, undated
      - Video (Box 67, Minidv 437_2411)
      - Video (Box 107, Minidv 437_2374)
    - Man Man Lai -- "Compositions / Improvisations", undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0089)
    - Marble, undated (Box 101, Hi8 437_2092)
    - "Marbles 500," Rotterdam and Bremen, undated (Box 122, Vhs 437_1141)
    - Maria Armane, Beth Sommerman, undated (Box 153, U-matic 437_0047)
    - Marika's group, undated (Box 122, Vhs 437_1145)
    - Masako Edit and Makeup, undated (Box 90, Hi8 437_1264)
    - Masako Fashion Show, undated (Box 89, Hi8 437_1249)
    - Merry X-mas, "Oder Halla" live, "Liebet Eure Eltern", undated (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0941)
    - Michael Keane Band, Old Bane, undated (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0943)
    - Mikee and Jack, undated (Box 140, Vhs 437_1864)
    - Ming Fay Exhibition, Gracie Gallery, undated (Box 99, Hi8 437_2007)
    - Ming Fay, Nam June Peik, undated (Box 144, Vhs 437_2154)
      This tape was repaired by the Media Preservation Unit in April, 2024.
    - Museum of Modern Art, undated (Box 85, Minidv 437_2276)
    - Morning songs for opera, undated (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0705)
    - Margaret Dewy Demo, undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0082)
    - Marlena Preda with Martha Wilson and Arleen Schloss, undated (Box 124, Vhs 437_1403)
    - Martini Beach Cyber-Gallery Show, NeeNas, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Morse, Hereford, Rodeo, undated (Box 103, Hi8 437_2197)
    - "Moster Mash" Performance, Greene Space, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Nachts In Der Stadt, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0376)
    - Neil Ralmik, The Kitchen, undated (Box 124, Vhs 437_1578)
    - New York Pamphlet, new How She, undated (Box 79, Audiocassette 437_0603)
    - New York Underground, undated (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0102)
    - Nik's set with Steve, undated (Box 91, Minidv 437_2293)
    - Nina, undated (Box 107, Minidv 437_2388)
    - "New York Women Artists," SUNY Art Gallery, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Newsounds Gallery Broadcast, CFRO-FM, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - "Nstallations" Performance, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - "Nude Theology" Performance, Club 57, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Nusrat Ali-Khan, Tipsy, undated (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_2413)
    - Opening Art Center, Jenny, undated (Box 101, Hi8 437_2090)
    - Paul Court Steno, undated (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0100)
    - Paul Shapiro Quarter, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0356)
    - Paula Nina Keyer, undated (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0313)
    - Pauline, Pri Wiel, undated (Box 141, Vhs 437_1921)
    - Peking Opera, undated
      - Pace University, Kwang Yu Fong (Box 134, U-matic 437_1692)
      - Loft Audio (Box 142, U-matic 437_2117)
    - Performance note cards, undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Performance Videos, undated (Box 120, Vhs 437_1183)
    - Peter Pinal, Hotel #4, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1480)
    - Performance at Club Anna, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1536)
    - Phoebe Legere, undated
      - Part one (Box 91, Hi8 437_1288)
      - Part two (Box 91, Hi8 437_1300)
    - Phoebe Legere #2, undated (Box 90, Minidv 437_2290)
    - Piano performance, Museum of Modern Art, undated (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0925)
    - Piano work, undated (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0699)
    - Piano work, undated (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0709)
    - "Plastic Bags" Performance -- Flyer and Artifact, undated (Box Shared Fales 115, Folder 12)
    - Poetry of Robert Stock, Jefferson Market Church, undated (Box 99, Hi8 437_2008)
    - Portrait of Warhol, undated (Box 82, Minidv 437_2294)
    - "A Process Demonstration," Anthony Forma, undated (Box 156, Half inch video reel 437_1959)
      Presented by Last Century
    - Professional performance, undated (Box 88, Minidv 437_0979)
    - Quiana Demo, Glen, undated (Box 116, U-matic 437_1077)
    - R.L., Christa, undated (Box 88, Minidv 437_0987)
    - Raw footage and special effects from Kitchen, undated (Box 140, U-matic 437_1881)
    - Records, Crista Lorne, undated (Box 76, Audiocassette 437_0496)
    - Rhys Chatham, The Kitchen, undated
      - Video (Box 98, Hi8 437_1996)
      - Video (Box 90, Hi8 437_1261)
    - Rhythm box, Workshop before Berlin, undated (Box 88, Audiocassette 437_0952)
    - Rhythm pause, Nina Hagen from Berlin, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0363)
    - Reunion, undated (Box 94, Hi8 437_1375)
    - Roberta Berman #1, Andy Warhol, A Portrait #1, undated (Box 80, Minidv 437_2287)
    - Roche, Holly #1, undated (Box 107, Minidv 437_2390)
    - Rough mix, SFX sampler, undated (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0902)
    - "The Red Spot" Event, undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - "Science Fiction," Paul Gabor, undated (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0107)
    - Scott Fisher, Koker #7, undated (Box 104, Hi8 437_2222)
    - Sensation, undated (Box 106, Minidv 437_2321)
    - Shadows Demo for Alan Garfield's friend, Charles' piece, undated (Box 143, Vhs 437_1928)
    - Shu Uemura, undated (Box 128, Vhs 437_1581)
    - Shu Uemura, Holly lips, undated (Box 89, Minidv 437_0998)
    - Shozo Shimamoto at Kazuko Gallery, Kwag Yu, undated (Box 93, Hi8 437_1368)
    - Snakes of Spain with Introduction by Arleen, undated (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0184)
    - Sofia, undated
      - Part one (Box 106, Minidv 437_2344)
      - Part two (Box 106, Minidv 437_2345)
      - Part three (Box 106, Minidv 437_2343)
    - Sorry Lee Lewis, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0361)
    - Sound la other side, undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0087)
    - Spanish rock, undated (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0375)
    - Spanish songs of the Renaissance -- Victoria de Los Angeles, Agnus Dei, Joaquin des Prez, undated (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0345)
    - "Spring Fever at Moda City" Performance, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - "SRS Show" with Sur Rodney (Sur), undated (Box 114, Vhs 437_1049)
      Directed by Gervaise Soeurouge
    - Stephen Kaplin, Unfinished Eye, undated (Box 89, Minidv 437_1015)
    - Steve Black, undated (Box 88, Minidv 437_2282)
    - Steve Reic, Phil Glass, undated (Box 135, Vhs 437_1701)
    - Stuart, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1478)
    - Sweetheart Ronald Parkins, undated (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0339)
    - Swiss Moroccan, Davidi, undated (Box 115, Vhs 437_1177)
    - "Ten Minutes to A," Pyramid Club, undated (Box 10, Folder 45, Box 64, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 6)
    - Test Pattern -- Stuart Copy, undated (Box 71, Audiocassette 437_0275)
    - Test pressing, Tartown Records, undated (Box 66, Audiocassette 437_0083)
    - This TLM, undated (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0156)
    - Thurs. Tom, Barbara, Hedda, undated (Box 107, Minidv 437_2396)
    - Tirey Tirey, undated (Box 70, Audiocassette 437_0258)
    - Tom Buckner, undated (Box 115, Vhs 437_1067)
    - Tom Kay, undated (Box 111, 1 inch video reel 437_2270)
    - Tomie Hahn, undated (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_0119)
    - Tonino -- Le Sauvagion, First Night, undated; cuid44180 (Box 151, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0003)
    - Tuart #2, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1516)
    - Ulysses -- "That's it!', undated (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0318)
    - The Velvet Underground Live, undated (Box 87, Audiocassette 437_0939)
    - Victor show, undated (Box 130, Vhs 437_1633)
    - Video Performance, Robert Freidus Gallery, undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - "Visages" Benefit for the Interactive Art Library System, Danceteria, undated (Box 10, Folder 47, Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Vocal range chant, undated (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0775)
    - "Voyager II -- Plasma Wave Sounds", undated
      - "Passing by Saturn", undated (Box 83, Audiocassette 437_0776)
      - Gretta Wing Miller, undated (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0387)
    - Warhol #1, undated (Box 106, Minidv 437_2315)
    - Warmup, undated (Box 88, Audiocassette 437_0949)
    - Water wave sounds, undated (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0882)
    - Waylan Country, undated (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0315)
    - "X-35," Plexus, undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Zatar, undated
      - "Here on Earth" (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0158)
      - "Peace," "Aurora" (Box 73, Audiocassette 437_0338)
    - Zeitgeschehen Peinlich, undated (Box 157, Audiocassette 437_0147)
    - ZOW, undated (Box 72, Audiocassette 437_0325)
- Series II. Video and Film Works, 1975-2015; 79.9 Linear Feet in 42 cassette boxes, 36 record cartons, 8 manuscript boxes, 4 LP boxes, 3 flat boxes, and 2 flat files; 195 VHS; 133 U-matic; 111 Hi8; 85 audiocassettes; 70 MiniDV; 14 Half_Inch_Video_Reel; 6 Quarter_Inch_Audio_Reel; 4 1_Inch_Video_Reel; 3 Betamax; 2 Betacam_SP; 2 DAT; 10.2 Gigabytes in 36 digital files
  Series II. Video and Film Works contains analog, digital, and paper materials related to Arleen Schloss' film, video, and television works. Schloss' films in this series include 30 Seconds (1983), Glenn Branca Symphony No. 4 / Physics (1984), It's A Live Laser (1985), A National Geographic (1989), Sun Daze Away (circa 1988-1992), Art Around the Park (1990-1998), From Kepler 2 Cyberspace: Virtual Worlds / Digital Dreams (1993), and Windows of Chance / Change (circa 1998). Her television work includes ID / It's Dance (1987-1989) and the Nickelodeon series Eureeka's Castle (1989-1990).
  Analog and digital audiovisual recordings include both masters and dubs of finished works, source materials such as interviews and event coverage, and recordings used in production such as graphics, audio samples, and credits. Paper production files include a wide variety of documentation, including photographs and video stills, graphics, grant proposals, project timelines, budgetary documents, production and licensing contracts, receipts and invoices, and ephemera from screenings and festivals. This series also includes footage of Schloss' travels, as well as ephemera, marketing materials, and invoices related to Studio A, Schloss' video production studio that she ran out of her Soho loft.
  Series II. Video and Film Works is arranged into four subseries:
  Subseries II.A Windows of Chance / Change Subseries II.B Art Around the Park Subseries II.C Travel Footage Subseries II.D Works by Date
  - Subseries II.A: Windows of Chance / Change, 1989-2000